[Music]
[Música]
Okay, uh, let's see, let's comment, let's
bueno eh A ver vamos a comentar vamos a
comment on something, okay, let's
comentar una movida vale vamos a
comment on this thing. Okay, I have
comentar esta movida Okay Eh tengo
exclusive statements from Lalii,
declaraciones en exclusivas de lalii
this would be Lali's response to everything
esta sería la respuesta de Lali a todo
that's happened in the last few days, to
lo que ha pasado en los últimos días a
the Ricky Eddie thread, to the
el hilo de Ricky Eddie a el hilo de la
Ricky Eddie's girlfriend thread, I'm not going to
novia de Ricky Eddie no voy a volver a
read the entire threads again because we already
leerlos los hilos completos porque ya
read them and you have an excerpt about
los leímos y tenéis un extracto sobre
that, yes, I wanted to comment a little on the
eso sí que quería comentar un poco el
subject of some comments, no, I mean,
tema del de algunos comentarios no O sea
I understand that there are youtubers who have
yo entiendo que hay youtubers que tienen
their fandom, who have their people who
su fandom que tienen su gente que que
support them, continue and I would support them just the same, no matter what they
les apoya sigam y les apoyaría igual
do, not
camente hicieran lo que hicieran no e
when I'm giving information,
cuando yo estoy dando una información o
whether on a newscast or for example. Now
bien en un noticiero o por ejemplo Ahora
when I comment on the exclusive about Ali,
cuando comente la exclusiva sobre el Ali
no, and Ali's statements are
no y las declaraciones del Ali son
objective, okay, I mean, now I'm going to
objetivas vale o sea yo ahora os voy a
give you Ali's statements and it doesn't
dar las declaraciones del Ali y no
mean that they are my words
significa que sean palabras de mi boca
or that I agree or that they are
ni que yo esté de acuerdo ni que son
mine or that they are approved by me, they are
mías ni que son aprobadas por mí son
exclusive statements from Ali, without further ado, it
declaraciones de Ali en exclusiv sin más
may seem better to you, it may  seem
os podrá parecer mejor os podrá parecer
worse when I'm giving news
peor cuando yo estoy dando una noticia
in a tweet or on a newscast, they are
en un tweet o en un noticiero son
objective, they are also news, nothing more,
objetivas también son noticias sin más
okay, they are facts, okay. And then there are my
vale son hechos okay Y luego están mis
gossip videos, whether they are excerpts from live streams
vídeos de salseo ya sean extractos de
or videos from the
los directos o sean los vídeos del Canal
main Channel where I am giving my opinion, okay, I am
principal donde estoy opinando vale a mí
surprised that to this day
me sorprende que a día de hoy todavía la
people still do not know what a
gente no sepa de lo que trata un canal
gossip criticism channel is about, not a joke, and they
de críticas de salseo no de moñe y
still give me comments like,
todavía me pongan comentarios como pues
well, what a [ __ ], you are not objective. Of course I
vaya [__] no eres objetivo Claro que
am not, you are clear, touch your dick, that's
no lo soyes claro tócate la [__] es de
what opinions are about, saying what
lo que tratan las opiniones de decir lo
I think. Do you want to browse the
que yo pienso quieres Navegar de forma
internet safely and also access
segura en internet y además acceder a
all the content of your
todo el contenido de tus plataformas
favorite platforms like Netflix, HBO Max, or Disney
favoritas como Netflix hbo Max o Disney
Plus? cyberghost VPN And I don't know if you
Plus cyberghost VPN Y es que no sé si lo
know, but there is content that is not available in your country
sabes pero hay contenidos que en tu país
and with this
no están disponibles y con este
little trick you can access all the
truquillo puedes acceder a todo el
content wherever you are? I don't know if you
contenido estés donde estés no sé si
know what a VPN is, but it is an
sabes lo que es una VPN pero es una
extension that you put on your internet
extensión que le pones a tu internet con
that masks your IP and apart from
la que enmascara la IP y aparte de
browsing completely safely and anonymously
Navegar completamente seguro y anónimo
without anyone being able to know who you are and
sin que nadie pueda saber quién eres y
where you are, it helps you access
dónde estás Te sirve para acceder a
some  content that is blocked
algunos contenidos que están bloqueados
in your country there are movies and series on your
en tu país hay películas y series en tus
favorite platforms that are not
plataformas favoritas que no están
available there are television programs
disponibles hay programas de televisión
for example on Mediaset content that if you
por ejemplo en mediaset contenido que si
try to watch them outside of Spain they have
los intentas ver fuera de España tienen
a geoblock that does not allow you Well
un geobloqueo que no te lo permite Pues
with Cyber ​​Ghost VPN that is over Apart
con Cyber Ghost VPN eso se acabó Aparte
from being protected and browsing
de estar protegido y navegando bajo el
anonymously you will be able to access
anonimato podrás acceder a los
content from all over the planet you will also
contenidos de todo el planeta además
have Total privacy since it keeps
tendrás privacidad Total ya que mantiene
your connection private and protects your
tu conexión en privado y protege tus
data ultrafast speed to
datos velocidad ultrarápida para
eliminate the lake in any
eliminar el lago en cualquier juego
online game with which you can enjoy live
online con los que podrás disfrutar de
streams without interruptions and as I have already
directos sin interrupciones y como ya os
told you Freedom to access all the
he dicho Libertad para acceder a todo el
content on the planet wherever and whenever you
contenido del planeta dónde y cuando
want also Take advantage of a whole 83%
quieras además Aprovecha todo un 83 por
discount using the link that I
de descuento utilizando el enlace que te
leave you in the description of this video and be
dejo en la descripción de este vídeo y
careful because you can try CyberGhost VPN
ojo porque puedes probar cyberghost VPN
45 days without obligation and if you are not
45 días sin compromiso y si no te
convinced you ask for a refund and they
convence pides el reembolso y te
will give you your belly back So don't wait
devuelven la panza Así que no esperes
any longer to protect your connection and improve
más para proteger tu conexión y aumentar
your internet experience run and
tu experiencia en internet corre yle
click on the link in the description and take
click al enlace de la descripción y
advantage of this super offer Cyber ​​Ghost
aprovecha esta superoferta Cyber Ghost
VPN to browse completely free and
VPN para navegar completamente libre y
secure we continue with the video but it's that
seguro seguimos con el vídeo no pero es
you do not  you get along well with Ricky Eddie
que tú no te llevas bien con Ricky Eddie
you have a problem with Ricky Eddie are
tú tienes un problema con Ricky Eddie
you going to twist to the point of supporting
vas a retorcer hasta el punto de apoyar
Ali well let's see are you going to forgive me one
a Ali bueno a ver me vas a perdonar una
thing with Ricky and Eddie eh what I had
cosa yo con Ricky y Eddie eh lo que tuve
the discussions that we have for me are
las discusiones que tenemos para mí son
content I don't know if you guys I
contenido yo no sé si ustedes Yo
understand that every fan of every youtuber
entiendo que cada fan de cada youtuber
for example Ricky Eddie's fans
por ejemplo los fans de Ricky Eddie pues
see me as the enemy or the one who
me tienen como el enemigo o el que se
messes with Ricky I don't know but I argue
mete con Ricky No lo sé pero yo discuto
Well I think there are 28 youtubers a day
Pues creo que son 28 youtubers al día
so for me none of them have
entonces para mí ninguno tiene la
enough stature to be an
envergadura suficiente como para ser un
enemy for me to hate them to
enemigo para que yo le tenga odio para
have them for me Ricky for me there was a
que tenga a mí Ricky para mí hubo un
comment some comments in which
comentario unos comentarios en los que
for me he crossed the line of the personal He
para mí traspasó la línea de lo personal
apologized for them and honestly I haven't even
Se disculpó por ellos y sinceramente ni
remembered it again or rather eh That's it, it's
lo he vuelto a recordar o sea eh Ya está
not important enough for
no tiene la importancia suficiente para
me for me to lie to be
mí como para yo mentir por estar en
against him if I say something or I am giving my
contra de él si yo digo algo o estoy
opinion on something it's what I think and
opinando de algo es lo que yo pienso y
it's what I am seeing okay it makes me
es lo que yo estoy viendo vale a mí me
angry because then when
da coraje porque luego cuando pasa el
time passes he proves me right Like for
tiempo que me da la razón Como por
example that gives  just like the police stations in
ejemplo que da igual que las comisaría
Andorra close at 3 in the afternoon
de andorra cierren a las 3 de la tarde
okay there was no restraining order there was
vale no hubo orden de alejamiento no
no complaint eh Dallas Dallas
hubo ninguna denuncia eh a Dallas Dallas
could enter Andorra perfectly well he
podía entrar en andorra perfectamente no
was not reported he is not going to have to
estaba denunciado no le va a tener que
pay anything Do not go to jail there were no
pagar nada No vaya a la cárcel no hubo
hitmen okay it was an idea of ​​raed at a
sicarios vale fue una idea de raed en un
time when he was caught issimo
momento en el que estaba pillad issimo
no and and it was raed who went to
no y y fue raed el que entró en la
jail so about those things and about
cárcel entonces sobre esas cosas y sobre
those nonsense then when
esas tonterías luego cuando va pasando
time goes by nobody tells me anything then it
el tiempo nadie me dice nada no entonces
turns out that the other day Ricky a
Resulta ser que el otro día Ricky un
kiss to Alan forgive me for not stopping
beso a Alan perdonadme que no me pare
now while I'm giving the
ahora mientras que estoy dando la
exclusive okay eh I'll thank you later and
exclusiva vale eh luego os agradezco y
everything okay Ricky suddenly appears the
demás vale Ricky de repente aparece el
other day with a very long tweet tochs
otro día con un tweet larguísimo tochs
himo giving some explanations about the
himo dando unas explicaciones sobre los
audios that he was publishing I tell you they
audios que estaba publicando ya os digo
are in other tracts they are in
están en otros tractos están en la
Ricky's Twitter account I am not going to
cuenta de Twitter de Ricky No las voy a
repeat them again okay Ricky affirms in that
volver a repetir vale Ricky Afirma en
Taco that in those audios that we are going to
ese Taco que en esos audios que vamos a
listen to Lali recognizes that she invented the
escuchar Lali reconoce que se inventa la
rape or it is proven that Ali  he
violación o queda probado que el Ali se
makes up the rape okay And I told you
inventa la violación vale Y yo os digo
the other day that no, in those
el otro día que que no que en esos
audios if you listen to the audios
audios si tú escuchas los audios no está
Ali is not making up a rape nor does he
el Ali inventándose una violación ni
admit to having made it up which I
reconoce que se la haya inventado que
understand perfectly and I agree in
entiendo perfectamente y comparto de
fact that there are a lot of people who
hecho que haya un montón de gente que
when they listen to those audios and see that
cuando escucha esos audios y ve ese
tweet say wow How bad that is Lali what a bird what a bird I do
tweet dice [__] Qué mal que da Lali
n't know what I don't know
menuda pájara menuda no sé qué no sé
how much I understand okay but for me in
cuánto lo entiendo vale pero para mí en
those audios he is not admitting nor is he
esos audios no está reconociendo ni se
making up the rape That is not what
está inventando la violación No es eso
you hear in the audios in those
lo que se escucha en los audios en esos
audios he is doing everything
audios lo que está haciendo todo lo
possible to lie so that he doesn't get caught
posible por mentir para que no le pille
cheating among the youth
la infidelidad en la chavaleria
we need a Marina to grow Well it
necesitamos una Marina para crecer Bueno
could be eh Hey it could happen to
pues podría ser eh Oye se podría dar a
me what turns me on like a ball in
mí lo que me calienta como balonazo en
the ear is your voice tasty old man Don't
la oreja es tu voz viejo sabroso No
stop talking I'm almost done okay okay okay I'll
pares de hablar que ya casi acabo vale
continue eh I'll continue you have
vale vale continúo eh continúo te va
time and there is a part Hello good
tiempo e hay una parte Hola buenas
evening Javi did you see that in the discussion they
noches Javi viste que en la tertulia
only said that Lali was a bad woman
solo dijeron que Lali era mala mujer
but they never mentioned that
pero jamás mencionaron que Ricky mintió
Ricky lied to the bully and nothing They have their opinion I have mine eh I don't know if it will be the same or I have not seen it eh I really have not seen it but well everyone has their opinion I have mine to me personally if in Ricky's tweet in
personalmente si en el tweet de Ricky en
all the Texaco he puts after I read the
todo el Texaco pone tras yo leer el
testimony of the kid minutes before it is
testimonio del chaval minutos antes
surprising how people distort what you
sorprende como la gente tergiversa lo
say just to get content and
que dices solo para sacar contenido y
when you only expose data without opinion
cuando solo expones datos sin opinión
they say that you are supporting someone but I do not care
dicen que estás apoyando a alguien pero
let's see but it
es que me da igual vamos a ver pero es
is an objective fact that Ricky puts
que es un dato objetivo que Ricky pone
a text eh And he says that in that text
un texto eh Y dice que en ese texto se
something is proven and then you listen to the
demuestra algo y luego tú escuchas los
audios and that is not proven In that I
audios y no se demuestra eso En eso
am defending Ali that Ali is not
estoy defendiendo a Ali que Ali no sea
a liar that Ali did not cheat on him that Ali
una mentirosa que el Ali no lo engañas
was not unfaithful that she did not
que el Ali no fuera infiel que no lo
cure him no no but it does not matter Look there
cuara no no pero es que da igual Mira
is a text in that tweet and so long no
hay un texto en ese tweet e tan tocho no
and there is a part that says Ricky after I
y hay una parte que dice Ricky tras yo
read the testimony of the kid minutes
leer el testimonio del chaval minutos
before it became clear to me that she acted in a
antes me quedó claro que ella actuó de
spiteful and voluntary manner so
forma despechada y voluntaria entonces
here Ricky  Eddie in the same text of the
aquí Ricky Eddie en el mismo texto del
piece of tweet that he writes is already
pedazo de tweet que escribe ya te está
telling you that from minute one he didn't
diciendo que desde el minuto uno no la
believe her okay I don't need to
creyó vale a mí no me hace falta que me
put it on Ricky here I mean I don't care I don't care
lo ponga Ricky aquí o sea me da igual me
em Ricky He didn't believe her Ricky
da igual em Ricky No la creyó Ricky la
made her put a thread on Twitter he stopped
la hizo poner un hilo en Twitter la dejó
following her and blocked her and deleted
de seguir y la bloqueó y y la borró
all her photos from Instagram Ricky He didn't
todas sus fotos del Instagram Ricky No
create her he stopped talking to her it was
la creó se dejó de hablar con ella fue
when Dallas started making a video
cuando Dallas empezó a hacer vídeo
when Ricky decides to take her home
cuando Ricky decide llevársela a su casa
and Ricky didn't believe that rape that
y Ricky que no se creía esa violación
his girlfriend had supposedly told him
que supuestamente le había contado su
Ricky makes a video with her
novia Ricky hace un vídeo con ella
our truth where he says that he is the one who
nuestra verdad donde dice que es él el
gives her a name and labels her
que le pone nombre y le pone la etiqueta
rape and that she accepts it and he
de violación y que ella la acepta y el
blames a guy as the rapist who
culpa de violador a un chaval que
was simply the one his girlfriend
simplemente era con el que su novia lo
had cuckolded him with I mean it's
había cuque o sea es que a mí me hace
really funny to me No no it's that
mucha gracia No no es que se le ha
Lali made it up I mean here the debate
inventado Lali o sea aquí el debate
now the pulse is whether Lali makes it up
ahora el pulso es si Lali se lo inventa
or Ricky makes it up I think
o se lo inventa Ricky yo creo que se lo
he makes it up so as not to accept that he's been
inventa él para no aceptar que le han
cuckolded okay hey  that
cuckeado vale oye que se le ha inventado
Lali and Ricky made up without believing her Ricky, without
Lali y Ricky sin creerla Ricky sin
believing her, went on for weeks saying that she had been
creerla se pegó semanas diciendo que la
raped. You have to see that we
habían violado que hay que ver que
were
estábamos
criticizing me. I uploaded a video that the
criticándome yo sube un vídeo que que el
video was based, okay, on some
vídeo estaba basado vale en unas
conversations, eh, that people
conversaciones eh que a mí gente del
close to Ali told me about. Okay, there are
entorno del Ali me comentó vale a mí hay
people close to Ali who
gente del entorno del Ali que me
contacted me and
contactó y me enseñó conversaciones de
showed me conversations between Ali and me that were very similar to these that they falsified. Okay, it's true that the ones that went viral were a montage but they perfectly represented the real ones. Okay, look at what Ricky told me in my video, I mean, in this video, practically
vídeo o sea en este vídeo prácticamente
what I was exposing, you can
yo lo que estaba exponiendo lo podéis
see it's on the main channel. Okay,
ver está en el canal principal vale
Ricky Eddie, your girlfriend cheated on you. Here's
Ricky Eddie tu novia te ha engañado aquí
all the evidence in this video. What I
todas la pruebas en este vídeo yo lo que
'm saying is that she hasn't been
estoy contando es que al al no la han
raped. That you're both lying
violado que estáis los dos mintiendo
about the rape. Okay, and you came along,
sobre la violación vale Y llegaste tú
Ricky Eddie, and you told me that even you, who have
Ricky Edi y me dijiste que hasta tú que
always had access and the ability to
siempre has tenido acceso y capacidad de
ask me personally so as not to
preguntarme personalmente para no
taint a story full of
manchar una historia llena de [__]
unknown [ __ ], have been able to publish
desconocida haya sido capaz de publicar
something like that. I'm very disappointed here. You
algo así me decepciona muchísimo aquí tú
wanted me to.  we followed the story that
querías que te siguiéramos el cuento de
your girlfriend had been raped that
que a tu novia le habían violado de que
you hadn't been cheated on and now
no te habían puesto los cuernos y ahora
you want the blame for the whole
te apetece que ahora la culpa de todo el
rape invention to be Ali's well
invento de la violación sea de Ali pues
no it was both of their faults it was the
no la culpa fue de los dos la culpa fue
two of them who sat down and recorded the
de los dos que se sentaron y grabaron el
video blaming an innocent kid for
videíto culpando a un chaval Inocente de
a rape it wasn't your idea it was
una violación fuera idea tuya fuera idea
Lali's idea for me in those audios for me
de Lali para mí en esos audios para mí
in those audios what is being told
en esos audios lo que se está contando
what Lali is doing in the first one
lo que Lali está haciendo en el primero
is having a good time with the guy who
es pasándoselo bien con el tío que le
is cheating on her man Ricky He does
está poniendo los cuernos hombre Ricky
n't believe it at first but as soon as he
No se la cree al inicio Pero en cuanto
sees that Dallas releases her video he sees the
ve que Dallas saca su vídeo é ve la
opportunity to use that story to go
oportunidad de usar Ese cuento para ir
against Dallas he cheated on himself to go against
contra Dallas se autoco por ir contra
Dallas Dallas released a video saying I
Dallas Dallas sacó un vídeo diciendo Yo
believe it she's been raped and Ricky He didn't
me la creo la han violado y Ricky No se
believe it Ricky left her he made her put up a
la creyó Ricky la dejó la hizo poner un
thread It's legal to hunt deer live
hilo Es legal cazar venados en directo
what a kiss eh Ricky He didn't create it
tremendo un beso eh Ricky No la creó
So what are you telling me now that it
Entonces de qué me estás contando ahora
was Lali The one who made it up and
de que fue Lali La que se lo inventa y
what and  that Lali is making it up, come on, I'm
qué y qué Lali se lo inventa vamos yo en
not seeing her
esos audios no estoy viendo que ella
mention rape in those audios, she's
mencione una violación ella lo que está
trying not to get caught, that she's been cheated on
es intentando que no la pillen que le
and she's a
han puesto los cuernos y es una
liar, she tells her friend, swear on your
mentirosa le dice a la amiga jura por tu
family if necessary, I don't know what, I don't know
familia si hace falta No sé qué no sé
how much, but she's not saying it was
cuánto pero ella no está diciendo que
rape, what she's
fuera una violación ella lo que está
saying is that she cheated on him,
diciendo es que le ha puesto los cuernos
that she cheated on him, at no point has
que lo ha engañado en ningún momento
she denied it, a video, three
ella ha negado eso un vídeo tres series
full series, well, she made a series, she made the
completas bueno hizo una serie hizo el
video, then she made a series, she deleted that series
vídeo luego hizo una serie esa serie la
and started recording it again. I mean,
borró y empezó a grabarlo otra vez O sea
but as far as I know, Ricky
pero hasta donde yo sé Ricky la la la
deletes the photos with her on Instagram, he
borra las fotos de de Instagram con ella
suggests that since he feels
le sugiere que como él se siente
humiliated, she should humiliate herself and I'll put up a
humillado que ella se humille y pongo un
thread and then he takes her to Andorra
hilo y luego se la lleva a andorra
when he doesn't believe her, he doesn't believe her
cuando él no la cree él no la cree
because in fact, right there in the text it
porque de hecho ahí en el propio texto
says so, okay, after I read the
lo dice vale tras yo leer el testimonio
kid's testimony minutes before, it became clear to me
del chaval minutos antes me quedó claro
that she acted spitefully and
que ella actuó de forma despechada y
voluntarily, he took her home and recorded
voluntaria se la llevó a su casa y grabó
a video saying it was rape
un vídeo diciendo que fue una violación
and when we were saying, Because we
y cuando nosotros decíamos Porque
had proof, because we  contacted
teníamos prueba porque nos contactó
people from Ali's entourage okay,
gente del entorno del Ali vale a mí me
people contacted me who even
contactó gente que incluso estuvo de
partied with her okay, they came to reproach
fiesta con ella vale venía a reprochar
us that we couldn't doubt that
noos que no podíamos poner en duda que
she had been raped that I couldn't tell
la habían violado que no podía yo contar
look at you This video in this video what I
miraros Este vídeo en este vídeo yo lo
'm saying is that Ali was
que estoy diciendo es que Ali le estaba
asking her friends she would
pidiendo a las amigas volvería a
repeat it This was true eh that Ali
repetirlo Esto fue verdad eh que Ali le
was asking her friends to
estaba pidiendo a las amigas que le
help her cover up the lie and now The
ayudasen a tapar la mentira y ahora El
kid well at that moment he messed up he
chaval pues en ese momento nos la lió me
blocked me and everything now The kid wants us to
bloqueó y todo ahora El chaval quiere
now follow the roll that it
que ahora le sigamos el rollo en que
's all her fault and that she was
toda la culpa es de ella y que fue ella
the only liar no no no that she
la única mentirosa no no no que ella te
cheated on you we know that she was unfaithful and
engañó lo sabemos que ella fue infiel y
that she wanted to do it again we know we know
que quería volver a hacerlo lo sabemos
from the first moment
lo sabemos desde el primer momento lo
we said it from day one Okay in those
dijimos desde el día Uno Vale en esos
audios what you're doing is making
audios lo que te estás es poniendo
excuses not because I knew No because I
excusas no porque yo sabía No porque yo
know I believed that she wasn't with
sab yo yo me creía que no estaba con
Ricky No because I drank too much and I got wasted on
Ricky No porque bebí mucho y me puse
poppers whatever you want I don't
hasta el culo de popper lo que quiera no
know if it says poppers or something else Okay anyway
sé si dice popper o otra cosa Vale total
now from  from here okay From
yo ahora a partir de aquí okay A partir
this moment on I have given you my opinion
de este momento ya os he dado mi opinión
Okay and I have made a clarification okay
Vale y os he hecho una aclaración okay
For me it is an objective fact that those
Para mí es un dato objetivo que esos
audios do not prove that
audios no demuestran que se lo inventas
she made it up second eh if she had the idea of
ella segundo eh si ella tuvo la idea de
inventing that there was no rape
inventándome que no había una violación
Okay and three he got angry even with the
Vale y tres se enfadaba incluso con la
people who said that it was not one and that we
gente que decíamos que no era una y que
had conversations Ricky that
teníamos converses Ricky esa cuada tan
wild sister left him suffering from dementia face
salvaje lo dejó sufriendo demencia cara
rolling with laughter face
revolviéndose de la risa cara
rolling with laughter apart He is bringing
revolviéndose de la risa aparte Está
up a subject that was not even being
sacando un tema que ni siquiera ahora
discussed right now it is not relevant
mismo se estaba hablando no ha venido a
and it is going to harm him now I
cuento y le va a perjudicar ahora os
will explain why okay he got
explico el porqué vale que él se
angry with the people who we said
enfadaba con la gente que decíamos
look at my video on the main Channel
miraros el vídeo mío del Canal principal
we said that there were conversations between
decíamos que había conversaciones de
Lali where Lali asked her friends I'm
Lali donde Lali le pedía a sus amigos es
going to put it dude I'm going to
que lo voy a poner tío es que lo voy a
put it dude I'm going to put it dude Look
poner tío es que lo voy a poner tío Mira
what's going on my kids like you and
qué pasa mi chavalería de como tú y
Ricky Ed if Ricky hadn't caught the
Ricky Ed si Ricky no llega a pillar al
al Lali would probably have left
al Lali seguramente hubiese dejado a
Ricky for another guy what happened
Ricky por otro chico lo que ha pasado
here  It's that when Ricky caught her Well, he
aquí es que cuando Ricky la ha pillado
put her out of her element and
Pues a ella le ha cortado el rollo y
she took the lie so far that she ca
ella ha llevado la mentira tan lejos que
n't go back I don't know if I
ya no puede volver atrás no sé si me
'm explaining myself well but I would
estoy explicando bien pero yo lo
sum it up as that she took the
resumiría en eso en que ha llevado la
lie so far because she felt
mentira tan lejos porque se ha sentido
bad about what she did to Ricky
mal con lo que le ha hecho a Ricky de
seeing him like that instead of saying Hey look well we
verlo así en vez de decirle Oye mira
have to break up because I
pues que lo tenemos que dejar porque me
'm seeing another guy in fact
estoy viendo con otro tío de hecho es
the story didn't fit at all at
que no cuadraba la historia para nada en
any time apart from saying that she doesn't
ningún momento aparte de decir que no
want to report him she starts to say
quiere denunciarlo ella se pone a contar
that well at first she wasn't
que bueno que al principio ella no era
aware that then her friends
consciente que luego sus amigas se lo
were telling her as the days went by that
fueron comentando al paso de los días
she became aware that she was
que ella fue consciente de que fue
raped when the days had passed and that
violada cuando ya pasaron los días y eso
is completely false that is
es completamente falso eso es
completely false not only because of what
completamente falso no solamente por lo
this conversation says that will have to be
que ponga esta conversación que habrá
confirmed it will have to be confirmed if it
que confirmarla habrá Que confirmar si
is real or not but because Lali your friends
es real o no sino porque Lali tus amigos
that conversation was not real But there were
esa conversación no era real Pero había
always similar conversations about all
conversaciones similares siempre de todo
the gossip about m why word Could I
el chisme de m por qué palabra Podría
look for a call please eh aunt Look it's not that this is
buscar llamada por favor eh tía Mira no
the false conversation eh there
es que está es la conversación falsa eh
is a conversation or rather this
hay una conversación o sea esta
conversation that they falsified is a
conversación que falsificaron es una
representation of one that is
representación de una que hay que es
real okay And also at some point in the
real vale Y además en algún punto del
video watch the whole thing if you want it's
vídeo miradlo entero si queréis que dura
22 minutes at some point in the video I
22 minutos en algún punto del vídeo lo
say it okay eh And then they got into it they
digo vale eh Y ahí se me la liaron me
both came to me on Twitter, Ricky and
vinieron por Twitter los dos Ricky y
her, both of them to lám when I was right
ella los dos a lám cuando yo tenía razón
but it's that I had seen
pero es que yo había visto las
Lali's conversations asking her
conversaciones de Lali pidiéndole a las
friends to help me lie to Ricky and
amigas ayudarme a mentirle a Ricky y
now no now we have that now Ricky
ahora no ahora tenemos que ahora Ricky
now Ricky feels like he's an
se ahora Ricky se le apetece que él es
innocent okay that he's
un es un inocente vale que él es
innocent and that and that she only made it up
inocente y que y que solo se lo inventó
and he was a poor man in love that no
ella y él era un pobre enamorado que no
no no no no You weren't a poor man
no no no no Tú no eras un pobre
in love you didn't believe her you left her
enamorado tú no la creíste tú la dejaste
and sent her to Zaragoza okay And
y la mandaste para zaragosza vale Y
when Dallas made a video of you saying they were
cuando Dallas te hizo un vídeo como
more in love with Dallas than
están más enamorado de Dallas que de
her, well then you told her to
ella pues entonces le dijiste que
come back And then you continued with
volviera Y entonces ahí ya tú seguiste
the rape thing, okay dude, I mean it's
el rollo de la violación está bien tío o
not that no I don't understand okay
sea es que no es que no no entiendo vale
Ali's statements Okay
declaraciones de Ali Okay declaraciones
Ali's statements Ali's statements okay These
del Ali declaraciones del Ali vale Estos
are Ali's words Okay  These are not
son las palabras del Ali Okay Estos no
my words or anything like that
son palabras mías ni nada por el estilo
eh to put you in context
eh para poneros un poco en contexto que
this will be another extract okay I will
esto será otro extracto vale lo lo
divide it in two because I have already made this
dividiré en dos porque he hecho ya esta
clarification at the beginning I will leave it long I do
aclaración al principio lo dejaré largo
n't know okay but to put you
No lo sé vale pero para poneros un poco
in context Lali has filed a complaint
en contexto Lali ha puesto una denuncia
for gender violence against Ricky this
de violencia de género a Ricky esto
means that Ricky is guilty
quiere decir que Ricky es culpable
obviously no then Ricky committed a
evidentemente no luego Ricky cometió un
crime by taking Lali's cell phone well
delito cogiéndole el móvil a Lali bueno
he acknowledged that it was a crime
eso reconoció él que eso era un delito
now justice will decide because
ahora lo decidirá la justicia porque
Lali has filed a complaint in Zaragoza
Lali ha puesto una denuncia en zaragosza
to the court Well being a mirror,
al juzgado Bueno al ser una espeja pues
this will go to the women's court
esto ira por el juzgado de la mujer la
Lila has reported him for
Lila lo ha denunciado por violencia de
gender violence and there are several issues it is not said
género y y hay varios temas no se dice
in the video of this girl from the other
en el vídeo de la chica esta del otro
day that there are insults threats and that she
día que hay insultos amenazas y que le
spoke badly to him there are a series of actions
hablaba mal hay una serie de acciones
that are provided apparently well that
que se aportan por lo visto pues que no
are not very appropriate and apart from that, well there
son muy apropiadas y aparte de eso pues
is Ricky's confession admitting
está la confesión de Ricky admitiendo
that he takes the phone away from her while she
que le quita el teléfono mientras que
sleeps eh to read her a series of
duerme eh para leerle una serie de
conversations No apart from this There is
conversaciones No aparte sobre esto Hay
also a problem for Ricky which is  e
un problema también para Ricky que es e
eh that he has given several different versions on
eh que él ha dado varias versiones sobre
the subject Because first he
el tema diferente Porque primero lo
admits it and then he keeps changing the version, it
reconoce y luego va cambiando la versión
wasn't I didn't read several conversations but
no era No leí varias conversaciones sino
I heard an audio no I didn't search his
que escuché un audio no no le registré
phone but I looked at it superficially anyway
el teléfono sino que lo miré por encima
and this will be decided by justice
en fin e esto ya lo decidirá la justicia
if it is a crime if they convict him or not okay eh what he
si es delito si lo condenan o no vale eh
says is that he searches her
el lo que dice es que le registra el
phone that he checks the
teléfono que comprueba en las
conversations that there is
conversaciones que existe una
infidelity And that he also asks her to
infidelidad Y que además le pide a ella
stop talking to her friends and to
que deje de hablarse con las amiga y que
block them and so on and he wants to continue with
las bloquee y demás y quiere seguir con
him Okay my opinion I prefer to wait for there to be
él Vale mi opinión Prefiero esperar que
a sentence to give it more
haya una sentencia para darla más
extensively okay eh Why Well because
extensamente vale eh Por qué Pues porque
in the Tudor issue for example Well I
en el tema de tudor por ejemplo Pues yo
thought they weren't going to convict him and they did
pensé que no lo iban a condenar y lo
convict him Okay so what do I know let's
condenaron Okay entonces yo que sé vamos
wait for justice to decide
a esperar que la justicia decida
obviously Ricky is innocent until
evidentemente Ricky es inocente hasta
justice says otherwise but but it has
que la justicia diga lo contrario pero
been very clumsy to me not only
pero me ha sido muy torpe no solamente
that it has been clumsy there is one thing
que haya sido torpe es que hay una cosa
that I don't understand okay And that is that being
que yo no entiendo vale Y es que estando
denounced according to you someone legally
denunciado según tú alguien legalmente
advises you to post a tweet with a huge
te aconseje ponerte un tweet con un
block  of text your girlfriend another with a
tochaco de texto tu novia otro con un
text that that text for me is from Ricky
texto que ese texto para mí es de Ricky
okay I don't know but for me it's from Ricky and
vale No lo sé pero para mí es de Ricky y
charging him with a crime publishing audios in which
imputarle delito publicar unos audios en
you are not a participant he says that he has been
los que tú no eres partícipe él dice que
advised and that they have given him
se asesorado y que le han dado permiso
legal permission I personally believe that although he
legal yo personalmente creo que aunque
may have the permission of one of the
pueda que tenga el permiso de una de las
parties and then nothing remains or
partes y luego pues no quede nada o lo
whatever mm a lawyer does not recommend
que sea mm un abogado no te recomienda
that you post that tweet I mean if you have
que pongas ese tweet O sea si tú tienes
a complaint from your ex the lawyer Although
una denuncia de tu ex el abogado Aunque
you are right and you can publish the
tú tengas razón y puedas publicar los
audios whatever the lawyer is always
audios lo que sea el abogado siempre te
going to tell you that it is better not to mention anything
va a decir que mejor no menciones nada
that you mention as little as possible and so on not
que menciones lo menos posible y demás
for nothing but also at the
no por nada sino que es que además al
end of the tweet he says and I have more if he
final del tweet dice y tengo más si
continues to get on my nerves or if he continues
sigue tocándome las narices o si sigue
publishing or if he answers this I have more
publicando o si contesta esto tengo más
things to show for me that I think
cosas que Mostrar para mí eso yo creo
that she can even throw in a
que incluso ella le puede meter una
veiled threat or whatever okay But
amenaza velada o lo que sea vale Pero
well each one can handle their issues as they
bueno cada uno que lleve sus temas como
want okay I am not an
quiera vale Yo no soy aquí ningún
expert here Okay What does she tell me okay
experto Okay Qué me comenta ella vale
what clarifications does she give me that she never
qué aclaraciones me hace ella que nunca
admits in those audios that she lied with that  she
en esos audios reconoce que mintió con
made up a rape okay in
que se inventó una violación vale que en
those audios no no no
esos audios no no se no se está
she's not making up any rape she's just
inventando ninguna violación que ella lo
lying to him she's never
que está es mintiéndole que ella nunca
denied that she lied to him a lot
ha negado que le mintió muchísimo que
she tells me eh Lali tells me this
ella me dice a mí Eh Esto me lo dice
This is not my opinion okay eh
Lali Esto no es una opinión mía vale eh
that she felt scared by
que ella e se sentía acojonada por la
Ricky's reaction and that she has never denied that he
reacción de Ricky y que nunca ha negado
lied to her about the infidelity that she
que le mintiera con la infidelidad que
has never denied that she
eso nunca lo ha negado que ella le
lied to him okay And you can hear it in those
mintió vale Y se puede escuchar en esos
audios but in those audios she doesn't claim
audios pero que en esos audios no Afirma
anything about rape and that evidently
nada de violación e que evidentemente
after what happened in recent days well
tras lo ocurrido estos últimos días Pues
there's an extension to that complaint eh due to
hay una ampliación a esa denuncia eh por
several accusations that Lali says that
varias acusaciones que dice Lali que
they're going to have to prove Okay
ellos van a tener que demostrar Okay
about the issue of the house when she
sobre el tema de la casa cuando ella
says that in a story she says I live
dice que en una historia ella dice vivo
5 minutes away we live 5 minutes away She
a 5 minutos vivimos a 5 minutos Ella
says that it's a way of expressing herself that it
dice que es una forma de expresarse que
's not literal 5 minutes that in Andorra It
no es literal 5 minutos que en andorra
's not that it's huge and evidently
No es que sea enorme y evidentemente
everything is practically close okay but
todo está prácticamente cerca vale pero
that she doesn't live 5 minutes away nor that
que no vive a 5 minutos ni que ni
she hasn't even looked for the house but that
siquiera ella ha buscado la casa sino
she a real estate agent  He looked for her
que ella una inmobiliaria le buscó la
house and it's not in her neighborhood. I mean, she
casa y que no es en su Barrio O sea ella
tells me that it's not in her neighborhood, that she doesn't
me dice que no es en su barrio que no se
run into him taking the dog out or anything like that
lo cruza sacando al perro ni nada por el
like they wrote, okay, about
estilo como han escrito ellos vale sobre
the harassment accusation that they make, she
la acusación de acoso que hacen él ella
says that this is a crime that they're going to have to
dice que esto es un delito que van a
prove and that she
tener que demostrar y que y que le
invites him to do it, so they're not going to have
invita a hacerlo o sea que no van a
any proof because it's a lie
tener ninguna prueba porque es mentira
that in Andorra there are many cameras and
que en andorra hay muchas cámaras y que
if it's true that she has
si es verdad que ella eh los ha
stalked them, she has stalked them on the
perseguido los ha perseguido por la
street or has constantly shown up
calle o se ha presentado constantemente
at places where they are, that it
en los sitios donde ellos estén que que
will be easy for her to prove it, okay, and
lo tendrá fácil para demostrarlo vale e
that she is in Andorra because she knows a
que ella está en andorra porque conoce a
lot of people and she never goes out to party alone,
mucha gente y nunca sale sola de fiesta
much less to look for them. That
y mucho menos para buscarlos a ellos Que
obviously they have crossed paths on
obviamente se han cruzado en alguna
occasion because in Andorra there are very few
ocasión porque en andorra hay muy poco
clubs. Or they only go to one, that is not
discoteca O solamente van a una eso no
clear to me. I don't know if there is one or
me ha quedado claro No sé si hay una o o
almost none, okay, but that there is a place,
casi ninguna vale pero que hay un sitio
okay, but obviously he has never
vale pero que evidentemente nunca la ha
pushed her or thrown a glass at her or
empujado ni le ha tirado un vaso ni lo
attacked her or anything like that,
ha agredido ni nada por el estilo ni
not verbally, okay. This is what
verbalmente tampoco vale Esto es lo que
she tells me about the cat issue.
me dice ella eh sobre el tema de la gata
and she says that there is a statement that she
e ella dice que hay una afirmación que
took in an injured cat she says that
es acogió a una gata herida dice que
this is a lie because the cat was
esto es mentira porque la gata se la
given to her and that there are stories in her e
regalaron y que hay historias en sus e
What are the highlighted stories called
Cómo se llaman las historias destacadas
no and that you go in there and you can see that
no y que os metéis ahí y podéis ver que
the cat no no was not an injured cat
la gata no no no era una gata herida
but rather a cat that was given to her
sino que es una gata que le regalaron
that they didn't They say in the statements
que no la Ellos dicen en los comunicados
that she brought the cat into Ricky's house without
que metió a la gata en casa de Ricky sin
warning she says that this is also a lie
avisar dice que esto también es mentira
because Ricky begged her to let him have it
porque Ricky le suplicaba que se la
okay and another statement is that she
dejase vale e otra afirmación es que
asked for the cat to see him meaning that she
pidió a la gata para verlo a él o sea
didn't care about the cat and that
que que no le importaba La gata y que
later she asked the cat to
luego le pidió a la gata que él se la
give it back to her so she could go see him okay
devolviera para poder ir a verlo vale
this is also a lie because in
que esto es mentira también porque de
fact when they went to pick up the cat it
hecho cuando fueron a recoger la gata no
wasn't her it was a friend Okay on the
fue ella fue una amiga Okay sobre el
subject of threats Okay on the subject
tema de las amenazas Okay sobre el tema
of threats the accusation of threats
de las amenaza la acusación de amenaza
uh what she explains is that she uh
eh lo que explica ella es que ella eh
a few months ago Well when she saw that
hace unos meses Pues cuando veía que
they uploaded like a lot of stories she
ellos subían como muchas historias retre
watered her cat and so on  she uploaded
regándola gata y demás pues ella subió
a cat to best friends in which in a
una gata a mejores amigos en el que en
rage she said something like if they
un enfado dijo algo así como si vuelven
rub it in my face again or upload photos of The
a restregarme o a subirme fotos de La
cat I'll upload Andorra and I'll kill them okay but
gata subo andorra y los mato vale pero
this was obviously not literal
que esto evidentemente no era literal
which is the typical one that says dude I'm going to
que es la típica que dice tío voy a
upload it I'll kill him you understand Well
subir lo mato me entiendes Bueno pues
Ricky apparently filed a complaint
Ricky por lo visto le puso una denuncia
at the police station Okay with with these
en la comisaría Okay con con estas
stories for friends like this thing of I'll
historias para amigos como que esto de
kill him I'll upload Andorra and I'll kill him was
lo mato subo andorra y lo mato era
literal okay it was a real threat and
literal vale que era una amenaza real y
also in that complaint this
que además en esa denuncia esto según
according to Lali uh that in this complaint that
según Lali eh que en esta denuncia que
Ricky filed he stated that Ali belonged
Ricky le puso afirmó que Ali pertenecía
to a Latin gang that Ali at the time
a una banda latina que Ali en su momento
went to testify at the police station about this
fue a declarar a la comisaría sobre este
matter and that they have not given him any more validity
tema y que no le han dado más valide
this case This was a long
este caso Esto fue hace un montón de
time ago and it has stayed there that no that they have not
tiempo y que se ha quedado ahí que no
paid attention to this complaint let's
que no le han hecho caso a esta denuncia
go Yes yes apparently in the complaint
vamos Sí sí por lo visto en la denuncia
Ricky said that these words were
dijo Ricky que estas palabras eran
literal those of I'll upload Andorra and I'll
literales los de subo andorra y me los
kill them If they continue to teach me wrong The cat
cargo Si siguen enseñándome mal La gata
SB I'll charge them okay And that it belonged  to a
SB los cargo vale Y que pertenecía a una
Latin band this This is what
banda latina esto Esto es lo que dice el
Ali says that Ricky filed the complaint eh And
Ali que Ricky puso la denuncia eh Y por
finally, regarding the accusation of
último sobre la acusación de denuncia
false accusation, what Ali tells me is that this
falsa lo que me dice Ali Es que esto
is another false accusation that she's going to have to
pues es otra acusación falsa que va a
prove Eh This is all in an
tener que demostrar Eh Esto todo en una
extension of the complaint eh In other words,
ampliación de la denuncia eh O sea ella
in the complaint she's going to include an extension
en la denuncia va a meter una ampliación
regarding the issue of publishing audios that don't
por el tema de publicar audios no que no
belong to Ricky, those audios are not
pertenecen a Ricky esos audios no forma
part of the conversation eh because of
parte de la conversación eh por por por
accusing her so widely in the media, of all
acusarla tan mediáticamente no de todas
these things and everything that's been
estas cosas y todo lo que le está
happening to him on his networks in the last few
pasando a al en sus redes en las últimas
hours, let her say that when
horas que eso ya que lo diga ella cuando
the time comes and of course there are
llegue el momento y y claro aquí hay
accusations of crimes here that she
imputaciones de delitos que ella
considers to be untrue
considera que que son que no son verdad
Okay and regarding the accusation of
Okay y sobre la acusación de denuncia
false accusation, what Lali says is that it
falsa lo que dice Lali es que
's obviously a lie that she never
evidentemente es mentira que nunca lo ha
reported it, only a
denunciado solamente ahora hace unas
few weeks ago These are statements
cuantas semanas Estos son declaraciones
from Ali Okay, yeah, she asked for my opinion,
del Ali Ok eh si me pedí mi opinión
man, I personally don't know if
hombre yo personalmente no sé si si
the complaint will have much scope or not
tendrá mucho recorrido la denuncia o no
Because I haven't seen the content that she has
Porque no he visto los contenidos que ha
included in the complaint Okay,
que ha metido en la denuncia Okay em al
apparently according to Andy  eh what there are
parecer según cuenta Andy eh lo que hay
are conversations of Ricky speaking to her
son conversaciones de Ricky hablándole
badly in a bad tone a series of
mal en un mal tono una serie de
publications of Ricky and excerpts in which he
publicaciones de Ricky y de extratos en
insults her I remember that there was like there
los que la insulta recuerdo que hay como
was like an intervention of Ricky
un había como una intervención de Ricky
in the delo podcast I think it is in which he
en el podcast de delo creo que es en el
talks about that it is not that Lali
que habla de que no es que Lali se la
sucks I don't know who I don't know how much no something
chupa no sé quién no sé cuánto no algo
like that eh There are also some insults on
así no eh También hay unos insultos en
Twitter and things like that eh but
Twitter y cosas por el estilo eh pero
apparently there are also some
por lo visto también hay unas salidas de
outbursts in some conversations that I don't
tono en unas conversaciones que esto no
know if this is true or not this apparently is
sé si es verdad o no esto por lo visto
presented in the complaint
se presenta en la denuncia la confesión
Ricky's confession about the phone issue and
de Ricky sobre el tema del teléfono y
now well there is going to be an expansion with
ahora pues va a haber una ampliación con
these things my opinion if I were Ricky
estas cosas mi opinión Yo si fuera Ricky
I think that I would have left this girl the
yo creo que a esta chica la hubiera
moment we broke up the
dejado en el momento que ya cortamos la
relationship and the whole thing I would have left
relación y todo el rollo hubiera dejado
the subject, I mean, don't even mention or debate
el tema o sea no ni menciones ni debates
about her or anything because I think it will
sobre ella ni nada porque creo que le va
complicate her life eh I mean whether you want it or not, whatever
a complicar la vida eh o sea quieras que
happens judicially it is a
no pase lo que pase judicialmente es un
problem I can't imagine any judge
problema No imagino a ningún juez
ruling in favor of Ricky let's see, I don't know
dándole la razón a Ricky a ver yo no sé
if this is true  the seriousness and the
si tiene esto la la gravedad y la
scope as for a conviction, you know,
envergadura como para una condena sabes
but man, they are headaches, they are
pero hombre son dolores de cabeza son
headaches, it was obvious that
dolores de cabeza es que era obvio que
she was going to report him at some point, I
ella lo iba a denunciar en algún momento
also said it, I also said it, eh, I
también lo dije también lo dije eh
also said it, but I went to file the
también lo dije pero fui a poner la
complaint before three. No, no, the
denuncia antes de las tres No no la
complaint was filed with a lawyer,
denuncia está puesta con con abogado
attorney, and all that stuff in
procurador y todas esas cosas en
Zaragoza, okay. It's not at the police station before
Zaragoza vale No es en comisaría antes
3 in the afternoon. I don't understand anything. I just would
de las 3 de la tarde no entiendo nada Yo
n't have gotten involved, I mean, I do
es que no me hubiera metido o sea es que
n't understand getting into such a mess and
no entiendo el meterte en un jaleo y
now it's impossible for anyone,
ahora es que es imposible que nadie que
no lawyer, eh, it's impossible for
ningún abogado eh es imposible que
any lawyer to recommend that you upload
ningún abogado te recomiend que subas
that on Twitter, it just doesn't make
eso twit sea es que no tiene sentido
any sense, it's complicating your life, eh, by
ninguno es complicarse la vida eh by the
face, man, by face, that drama started
face tío by the face ese drama empezó
because she wanted to deny Dallas. No, man, let's
por querer desmentir al Dallas No hombre
see. For me, eh, look, how
a ver Es que para mí eh fíjate tú qué
simple it would have been, she cheated on you,
sencillo hubiera sido te pone los
she made excuses, it's not that she
cuernos ella te pone excusas no es que
was very drunk, she was very high. I don't know
estaba muy borracha iba muy puesta No sé
what you want, see you later. And that's it
lo que tú quieras hasta luego Y ya está
and out and I'm not talking about her anymore, I don't
y fuera y no hablo más de ella ni le
talk to her or  nothing like that I don't talk to him
hablo ni nada por el estilo ni le hablo
or anything like that I
ni nada más por el estilo o sea te
mean he cheats on you he cheated on you over a
engaña te engañó durante un fin de
weekend and you caught him having conversations
semana y le pillaste unas conversaciones
where he wanted to keep cheating on you he
en las que querías seguir engañándote
wanted to keep seeing you at what
quería seguir quedando contigo en qué
point to contradict
momento para llevarle la contraria al
Dallas you start getting back with her and
Dallas te pones a volver con ella y
making videos saying that she was raped
hacer vídeos diciendo que la han violado
when you didn't believe her to recognize her in a
cuando tú no la creías a reconocer en un
video that you took her phone or rather if he does
vídeo que le has cogido el móvil o sea
n't say it
que que todavía si no lo llega a decir
in a video there's nothing because if he doesn't say it in a video there's nothing
en vídeo no hay nada es que si él no
dude and now he's not happy with that Yeah continue
tío y ya no contento con eso Si seguir
with the subject continue with the subject he
con el tema seguir con el tema hizo
also made a tweet where he said that she was abused he
tweet también donde dijo que fue abusada
made a tweet I can't get on
hizo twit Es que no puedo entrar en
Twitter dude I don't know what's wrong with him today but
Twitter tío no sé qué le pasa hoy pero
Twitter on the computer doesn't work it only works
el Twitter en el ordenador no va solo va
on the phone the same thing happens to you guys there's
en el móvil a ustedes pasa lo mismo hay
a tweet can you please send me the
un tweet me lo podéis mandar porfa la
screenshot I can't open Twitter
captura Es que no puedo abrir Twitter
wow I wanted to comment on that but I can't
wale lo quería comentar eso pero no
yeah I saw it let's see if tomorrow
puedo sí lo he vicho a ver si mañana
I change the browser what's going on dude I
cambia el navegador qué va tío es que lo
try to open Twitter with other
intento abrir el Twitter con otros
browsers and it doesn't work either dude I mean it doesn't work
navegadores y tampoco tío O sea no va
Twitter on the computer I don't know why he
Twitter en en ordenador no sé por qué le
grabbed his phone and asked him to stay away
agarro el móvil y le pide que se aleje
from his friends mind you this is important he keeps
de las amigas ojo que esto es importante
her away from her environment we'll see
la aleja de su entorno ya veremos a ver
if that's serious enough to constitute
si eso tiene la envergadura suficiente
a crime I don't know
como para un delito yo no lo sé la
honestly I don't want to make a fuss about these
verdad no quiero hacer porras con esos
issues they are sensitive issues But the only thing I will
temas son temas delicados Pero lo único
say is that these are issues that
que sí digo es que son temas que se
could have been avoided anyway now
podían haber evitado sea es que ahora
Nobody was talking about this issue eh
Nadie estaba hablando de ese tema eh
Delete the cache from your browser I've done that
Borra el carch del navegador lo he hecho
too man but let's see Anica can you
también tío pero a ver Anica me puedes
send me the screenshot of that tweet you
mandar por pasa la captura del del tweet
mentioned because I know there's
ese que me comenta porque yo sé que hay
a tweet where they made a video there
un tweet donde hicieron un vídeo en
was a video they made on
Twitter hubo un vídeo que hicieron en
Twitter where they justified
Twitter donde ellos justificaban el Por
why they didn't want to report the rapist
qué no querían denunciar al violador
but they didn't report
pero a Dallas sí que tampoco denunciaron
Dallas either do you remember do you remember there was
a Dallas os acordáis os acordáis que
a video on Twitter where they said no we're
hubo un vídeo en Twitter donde decían no
not going to report the rapist
al violador no lo vamos a denunciar
because we don't like reports but
porque no nos gustan las denuncias pero
Dallas Yes because he has called me an
a Dallas Sí porque nos ha me ha llama
abuser He never reported Dallas
maltratador No denunció a Dallas nunca
either and with all the balls there are
tampoco y con todos los cojon aos hay
people supporting him  to Ricky because he has
gente apoyando a Ricky porque ha
published three auto contest audios Okay
publicado tres audios autos contest Vale
and there are people giving it a like and How bad is
y y hay gente dándole like y Qué mala es
Lali Well yes, Lali is very bad but
Lali Pues sí pues Lali es muy mala pero
Ricky is not good either no anyway
Ricky tampoco es bueno no en fin
[Music]
[Música]